-咖啡  -谢谢
- Coffee. - Thank you.
-卡布其诺  -谢谢[意大利语]
- Cappuccino. - Grazie.
这杯美味的热苹果汁是莫妮卡的
And a nice, hot cider for Monica.
谢谢
Thank you.
瑞秋  为何我的肉桂棒上有橡皮擦
Rach, why does my cinnamon stick have an eraser?
原来是这样
That's why.
对不起
Sorry.
钱德勒
Chandler?
泰洛克小姐  你今天真漂亮
Miss Tedlock, you look lovely today.
我能说你这袖口长度真显身材吗
May I say that is a very flattering sleeve length on you.
科斯特力克先生希望你下班后到他办公室去
Mr. Costilick would like you to stop by his office today.
如果他是为搞笑备忘录的事
If it's about those prank memos,
那绝不是我干的  真的
I had nothing to do with them, really.
各位,
Hey, you guys!
钱德勒马上来  他说有天大的好消息
Chandler's coming and he has incredible news.
所以他来的时候我们就......
So when he gets here, let's all act, like, you know
不管了  这一定是很好的消息
Never mind. But it was gonna be really good.
到底怎么了...
What's going on?
今天和平常没什么两样
So it's a typical day at work...
然后艾尔叫我到他办公室
...and Big Al calls me into his office
说他要我当处理主管
and tells me he wants to make me processing supervisor.
-真是太好了  -恭喜...
- That is great! - Congratulations!
所以我就辞职了
So I quit.
为什么
Why?
为什么  因为这只是暂时的工作
Why? This was a temp job.
钱德勒  你已在公司五年了
Chandler,you've been there for five years.
我知道  但接受升职
I know, but if I took it,
不就代表承认这就是我的职业
I'd be admitting that this is what I do.
那不是能赚更多钱
Was it a lot more money?
我不在乎  我不想成为
Doesn't matter. I just don't want to be
在办公室坐到午夜
a guy who sits in his office until 12'o clock in the night...
担心"周净计"的那种人
...worrying about the WENUS.
"周净计"是啥
The "WENUS"?
"每周估计净值使用统计系统"
Weekly estimated net usage system.
这是处理用术语
It's a processing term.
这么回事啊
Oh, that WENUS.
你有何打算
What will you do?
我不知道  问题就在于我不知道想做什么
I don't know, that's the thing I don't know what I want to do.
我只知道我在那工作下去就永远想不明白
I just know I'm not going to figure it out working there.
我这有份活给你
I have something you can do!
我的新按摩客户史提夫
I have this new massage client, Steve.
不多说了  他开了一家餐厅
Anyway, he's opening up a restaurant...
他正在寻找主厨
...and he's looking for a head chef.
-你好  -你好.
- Hi, there.  -Hi.
我知道你是个厨师  而且我先想到你
I know. You're a chef and I thought of you first.
但钱德勒目前没有工作所以...
But Chandler's the one who needs a job right now,so....
我没有太多厨师的经验
I just don't have a lot of chef-ing experience.
除非那是家只卖吐司的餐厅
Unless it's an all-toast restaurant.
他想要什么菜色
What kind of food is he looking for?
他想要菜色丰富多变
He wants to do something eclectic.
因此他在找一个能创造出整个菜单的人
He's looking for someone who can create the entire menu.
-天啊  -很棒吧
- Oh my God! - I know!
所以你意下如何
So, what do you think?
谢了  菲比
Thanks. Pheebs.
-我觉得自己不适合戴白色厨师帽  -好吧
- I just don't see myself in a big, white hat. -Ok.
莫妮卡  你猜怎么着
Oh, Monica! Guess what?
你们能透过衬衫看见我的乳头吗
Can you see my nipples through this shirt?
看不见  但别担心  它们肯定还在
No, but don't worry. I'm sure they're still there.
你要上哪儿去  西装笔挺先生
Where are you going? Mr. suity man
我和罗伯·提曼博士有约
I have an appointment with Dr. Robert Pilman,
求职顾问阿哥哥
career counselor-a-go-go!
-阿哥哥是我加的  -求职顾问
- I added the "a-go-go." - Career counselor?
你们都已找到人生的方向
You guys all know what you want to do.
还没
I don't.
在客厅里的各位全都已找到人生的方向
You guys in the living room all know what you want to do.
你们有目标  有梦想  我却没有梦想
You have goals. You have dreams. I don't have a dream!
少见的"我没有一个梦想"演说
The lesser-known "I Don't Have a Dream" speech.
我爱我的人生  我爱我的人生
I love my life! I love my life!
布莱恩的歌
"Brian's Song"!
-见面的结果如何  -相当顺利
- The meeting went great? - So great!
他告诉我未来餐厅的位置
He showed me where the restaurant's gonna be.
就在第十街上有个温馨的小店面
It's this, it's this cute little place on 10th Street.
不太大也不太小  大小适中
Not too big, not too small. Just right.
前任老板是金发女人和几只熊吗
Was it formerly owned by a blond woman and some bears?
周一晚我要煮一餐让他品尝  算是面试
I'm cooking for him Monday night, kind of an audition.
菲比  他也要你在场
Phoebe, he wants you here.
这样对我有好处  因为你可以装作吃得很香
It's great for me. You can make yummy noises.
-你打算做什么  -吃得很香
- What are you gonna make? - Yummy noises.
那莫妮卡  你要做什么菜
And Monica, what are you gonna make?
我也不知道  但一定会很棒的
I don't know. It's gotta so be great.
我知道你可以做什么了  我知道
I know what you can make! I know!
你应该用那些东西做这个
You should make that thing with the stuff.
你知道用那些东西做的这个
You know that thing with the stuff?
好吧  我也不知道
Okay, I don't know.
各位  谁知道附近有约会的绝佳地点
Guys. Anyone know a good date place in the neighborhood?
东尼餐厅如何  吃下一公斤牛排就免费
How about Tony's? If you finish a 32-ounce steak, it's free.
有谁知道哪家不用带美洲豹过去的好餐厅
Anyone know a good place if you're not dating a puma?
-你要和谁约会  -是昆虫女吗
- Who are you going out with? - Is this the bug lady?
"我爱你  罗斯"
"I love you, Ross."
她叫希莉亚  不是昆虫女
Her name is Celia she's not a bug lady
她是博物馆的昆虫部主任
and she's curator of insect at the museum.
-你们打算做些什么  -出去吃晚餐
- What are you gonna do? - Go out to dinner...
然后带她回我的住处
...then bring her back to my place
带她看看我的猴子
and introduce her to my monkey.
他这不是在打比方
And he's not speaking metaphorically.
回你的住处啊  你有没有想...
So back to your place? You thinking maybe....
我不知道你啥意思
Well, I don't know....
我希望...
I'm hoping....
告诉你  那猴子是魅力十足
I'm telling you. That monkey is a chick magnet.
她一旦看见它可爱的小脸
She'll take one look at his cute, little face
然后一切就搞定
and it'll seal the deal.
希莉亚  别担心  它不会伤害你的
Celia, don't worry. He's not gonna hurt you!
用安抚的语调
Soothing tones.
-过来  马赛尔  -我受不了了
- Here, Marcel. - I can't stand this.
-它的爪子在我的  -好了  乖..
- He's got his claws on my - Yeah, all right.
试试这鲑鱼慕斯
Okay, try this salmon mousse.
好吃
Good.
比其他的鲑鱼慕斯好吃吗
Is it better than the other salmon mousse?
-更滑更柔  -是吗  这样更好吗
- It's creamier. -Yeah? Well, is that better?
我不知道  这是条搅成泡沫的鱼
I don't know. We're talking about whipped fish.
我能不吐出来就已经不错了
I'm just happy I'm keeping it down.
天啊  你怎么了
God, what happened to you?
8个半小时的天资测验
Eight and a half hours of aptitude tests...
智力测验  个性测验  我了解了什么
...intelligence tests, personality tests, and what do I learn?
"你适合在大型跨国公司
"You're suited for data processing
"数据处理部门方面发展"
for a large multinational corporation."
这太好了  因为你已知道该如何做
That's so great! You already know how to do that.
你们能相信吗
Can you believe it?
我不像是做那种酷工作的人吗
Don't I seem like I should be doing something cool?
我总是想像自己能做点事情
I just always pictured myself doing something....
了不得的事情
Something!
钱德勒  我知道
Chandler, I know, I know.
原来透过这件衬衫能看到你的乳头啊
Hey, you can see your nipples through this shirt.
给  这个或许能让你开心点
Here you go. Maybe this will cheer you up.
5小时前我吃了一颗葡萄
I had a grape about five hours ago,
所以我最好和你平分吃
so I better split this with you.
它本来就应该那么小  这是餐前开胃菜
It's supposed to be small. It's a pre-appetizer.
法国人称它为"阿姆兹布许"
The French call it an amuse-bouche.
这简直是太神奇了
Well, it is amusing.
温蒂  对  八点
Hi, Wendy. Yeah, 8:00.
我们不是说过吗  每小时十块
What did we say, $10 an hour?
很好  再见了
Okay, great. All right, I'll see you then.
什么每小时十块
$10 an hour for what?
我请餐厅里的女服务生帮忙
I ask one of the waitress from work, she's helping me.
服务生
Waitressing?
当然我考虑过你  但...
Of course I thought of you. But....
-但是...  -但是什么
- But.... - But, but....
但是今晚一定要做到完美  你知道吗
But it's just this night has to go just perfect, you know?
温蒂的经验丰富  是个职业服务生
Wendy's more of a professional waitress.
我应该继续保持业余的姿态
And I'm maintaining my amateur status
将来才能在奥运会上当服务生
so I can waitress in the Olympics.
我不想自吹自擂
I don't mean to brag,
但我1976年在因斯布鲁克当过服务生
but I waited tables at Innsbruck in '76.
来点阿姆兹布许
Amuse-bouche?
和我说话
Talk to me.
早上我坐地铁时发生了一件怪事
A weird thing happened on the train this morning
说下流话
Talk dirty.
-在这里  -对  来吧
- Here? - Come on. Come on.
说点火辣的
Say something hot.
什么  什么
What? What?
外阴
Vulva.
Vulva?
我当时好害怕  她吓了我一跳
I panicked, all right? She took me by surprise.
但也不算一败涂地  我们以爱抚收场
But it wasn't a total loss. We ended up cuddling.
爱抚了啊  几次
You cuddled? How many times?
闭嘴  感觉还不错
Shut up. It was nice.
我只是不是那种讲下流话的人
I just don't think I'm a dirty-talking kind of guy.
有什么啊  你只要说出你想对她如何
What's the big deal? Just say what you wanna do to her.
或是你想她对你如何
Or what you want her to do to you.
或是别人想对彼此如何
Or what other people might be doing to each other.
这样吧  对我说两句试试
I'll tell you what. Try something on me.
你是在开玩笑对吧
Please be kidding.
有何不可
Why not?
只要闭上眼睛告诉我  现在你想干什么
Just close your eyes and tell me what you'd like to be doing right now.
好吧...我在我的住处
Ok, I'm in my apartment....
-然后呢  -你不在那里.
- Yeah, what else? - You're not there.
-我们没有这次谈话  -好吧  那我先来
- We're not having this conversation. - All right, I'll start.
-乔伊  别这样  -来嘛  准备好
- Joey, please... - Come on, ready, look.
罗斯
Oh, Ross...
你让我欲火焚身  我要你马上舔我
...you get me so hot. I want your lips on me now.
-该你了  -我看还是算了吧
- Now you say something. - I really don't think so.
-你喜欢她对吧  -对
- You like this woman, right? - Yeah.
-想再见到她对吗  -当然
- You wanna see her again, right? - Sure.
如果你对我都说不出下流话
If you can't talk dirty to me,
你如何对她说呢
how will you talk dirty to her?
现在告诉我你想爱抚我的屁股
Now tell me you wanna caress my butt!
好吧  转过去
Okay, turn around.
我说话时不想你盯着我看
I don't want you staring at me while I'm doing this.
好吧  我不看  说吧
All right, I'm not looking. Go ahead.
我要...
I want Okay, I want...
用我的双唇感觉你那火热光滑的皮肤
...to feel your hot, soft skin with my lips.
这就对了  继续
There you go. Keep going, keep going.
我要用我的舌头...
I want to take my tongue and
快说啊
Say it.
快说
Say it!
舔遍你的全身
run it all over your body...
直到你颤抖...
... until you're trembling with
然后呢
With?
-说来好笑  -你不会相信的
- Funny story. - You're not gonna believe this.
没事  我一向赞成你们两个小子交往
It's Ok, I was always rooting for you two kids to get together.
钱德勒  你睡觉时
Chandler, while you were sleeping,
以前的公司又打电话来
that guy from your old job called again.
-又打来  -一遍又一遍
- Again? - And again and again and again.
喂  又打来了
Hello. And again.
嘿  科斯特林克先生  15楼的情况如何
Hey, Mr. Costilick. How's life on the 15th floor?
我也想念你.
Yeah, I miss you too.
对  偷自己家里的笔不够刺激
Yeah. It's a lot less satisfying to steal pens from your own home.
你真慷慨  但这不是钱的问题
That's very generous. But this isn't about the money.
我需要的不只是一份工作
I need something more than a job.
我要的是我真正想要的
I need something I really care about
这津贴不包含在你稍早提过的年终红利里
That's on top of the year-end bonus you metioned earlier?
你的梦想...
Your dream!
听着  艾尔  我不是在故意为难你
Look, Al, I'm not playing hardball here, okay?
这不是交涉  这叫拒绝
This is not a negotiation. This is a rejection!
不不不  别再讲数字了
No, no, no Stop saying numbers!
告诉你  你看错人了  你看错人了
I'm telling you, you've got the wrong guy!
星期一见
I'll see you Monday!
好大  比小格子大多了
Wow! It's huge! It's so much bigger than the cubicle.
这是一个格间
This is a cube!
看这里
Look at this.
你有窗户
You have a window!
没错  还有美丽的风景...
Yes, indeed-y. With a beautiful view of
看  有人在小便
Look! That guy's peeing!
风景看够了  看这个
That's enough of the view. Check this out.
坐下
Okay, sit down here.
这个最酷,
This is great.
-准备好没  -好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
海伦  能进来一下吗
Helen, could you come in here?
谢谢你  海伦  没事了
Thank you, Helen. That'll be all.
最后一次了  我保证
Last time I do that. I promise.
温蒂  我们约好的
Wendy, We had a deal.
你答应过我
Yeah, you promised.
温蒂  温蒂  温蒂
Wendy! Wendy! Wendy!
-那是谁  -叛徒温蒂
- Who was that? - Wendy bailed.
我没服务生了
I have no waitress.
真是太糟糕了  再见
That's too bad. Bye-bye.
一小时十元  一小时十二元
Ten dollars an hour! Twelve dollars an hour!
莫妮卡  我也希望能帮你
Mon, I wish I could,
但我已经计划好去走走
but I've made plans to walk around.
瑞秋  你逃婚之后是我一直在支持你
Rachel. When you ran out on your wedding, I was there for you.
我让你有地方住
I put a roof over your head!
如果这样对你仍毫无意义...
If that means nothing to you....
一小时二十元
Twenty dollars an hour.
成交
Done.
欢迎光临莫妮卡家  我能帮您拿外套吗
Hello. Welcome to Monica's. May I take your coat?
-嗨  史提夫  -嗨  莫妮卡
- Hi, Steve. - Hello, Monica.
你好  招待小姐
Hello, greeter girl.
-她叫瑞秋  -好吧  随便
- This is Rachel. - Yeah, okay.
味道好香
Everything smells so delicious.
我已忘记上次闻到这种美味的混合物是...
I can't remember ever smelling such a delicious combination of
好吧  香味
Okay, smells.
-这房子真漂亮  -谢谢  想参观一下吗
- It's a lovely apartment. - Thank you. Would you like a tour?
我只是客套一下  但好吧
I was just being polite, but all right.
-怎么了  -坐计程车来时
- What's up? - In the cab on the way over...
史提夫抽了一根大麻烟
...Steve blazed up a doobie.
什么
What?
-抽了一根大麻之类的...  -好了  我懂
- Smoked a joint, you know? Lit a bone. Weed, hemp, ganja - Ok.
我跟你统一战线  切奇
I'm with you, Cheech.
这里很干燥吗
Is it dry in here?
我来为您倒杯酒
Let me get you some wine.
我们可以上第一道菜了
I think we're ready for our first course too.
这些是石虾小方饺蘸芫萎调味酱
These are rock shrimp ravioli in a cilantro ponzu sauce...
加上一点点...
...with just a touch of minced...
碎姜
...ginger.
打我屁股叫我朱蒂吧
Well, smack my ass and call me Judy!
-真是太好吃了  -我真高兴你喜欢
- These are fantastic! - Gosh! I'm so glad you liked them.
喜欢吗  我可以吃下上百个
Like them? I could eat 100 of them!
只有这一些
That's all there is of these...
但再过8分半就有美味的洋葱馅饼吃
...but in a few minutes, we'll serve some delicious onion tartlets.
"馅饼..."
"Tartlets?"
"Tartlets."
"馅饼..."
文字都已失去意义
Word has lost all meaning.
请问需要任何帮忙吗
Excuse me. Can I help you with anything?
你看  我也不知道自己在找什么
You know, I don't know what I'm looking for.
酷  墨西哥馅饼
Cool! Taco shells!
这个就像是玉米卷饼一样  你懂吗
They're like a little corn envelope, you know?
-你不该影响食欲  -糖片
- You don't wanna spoil your appetite. - Hey, Sugar-O's!
你知道吗  再等6分钟半
You know, if you just wait another 6 1/2 minutes
干酪通心面  我们要做这个
Macaroni and cheese! We gotta make this!
-不  我们不做  -哦  好吧
- No, we don't. - Oh, okay.
抱歉
Sorry.
我们何不坐这儿
Why don't you just have a seat here?
-小熊软糖给我  -不
- Give me the gummy bears. - No.
-把它们给我  -好吧  分你一半
- Give them to me. - We'll share.
-不  小熊给我  -那就一点不分你
- No. Give me the bears. - Then you can't have any.
-把他们给我  -这样不值得
- Give them to me! - It's not worth it!
小熊落水了  他们快淹死了
Bears overboard! They're drowning!
伙计们  抓住糖片逃命啊
Hey, fellas, grab onto a Sugar-O! Save yourselves!
救命啊....我溺水了
Help! Help, I'm drowning!
-我受够了  晚餐结束  -什么  为什么
- That's it! Dinner is over! - What! Why?
为什么
Why?
这种机会我已等了七年
I've waited seven years for an opportunity like this...
而你却等不了四分半钟之后再吃洋葱馅饼
...and you can't wait 4 1/2 minutes for a stupid tartlet?
你不会想为那种人工作的
You don't wanna work for that guy like that.
我知道  我只是以为我的机会来了
I know, I just thought that this was it.
不要担心  你是个了不起的厨师
You get it. You're an amazing chef.
那些赞美的声音我不是装的
Those yummy noises? I wasn't faking.
和希莉亚的状况如何
So, how did it go with Celia?
-简直是不可思议  -干得好  罗斯
- I was unbelievable. - All right, Ross!
我是讲下流话的行家
I was the James Michener of dirty talk.
那简直是天下最具巧思的下流话
It was the most elaborate filth you have ever heard.
有人物  主线
I mean, there were characters, plot lines,
剧情  主题
themes, a motif.
其中一段连村民都冒出来了
At one point, there were villagers.
然后呢
And?
下流话讲完后已经有点晚了
By the time we finished all the dirty talk it was kind of late
而且我们也有点没劲了  所以
and we were kind of exhausted, so...
-你们爱抚  -那种感觉好好
- You cuddled. - Yeah, which was nice.
你们想看晚场电影吗
Do you guys want to try to catch a late movie?
或许吧  但我们不是该等钱德勒吗
Maybe, but shouldn't we wait for Chandler?
他到底跑哪儿去了
Where the hell is he?
对  朋友  我知道现在几点
Yes, friends, I know what time it is...
但我看着"周净计"  它让我相当不高兴
...but I'm looking at the WENUS and I'm not happy!
我跟你讲清楚
Let me tell you something.
你会在乎的  因为我在乎
You will care about it because I care about it.
明白了吗  很好
Got it? Good!
这样如何
How's this?
不好意思  这边呢
Sorry. How about over here?
这就说明有效果了.
That means it's working.
-痛不痛  -不痛.
- Does this hurt? - No.
这样呢
How about this?
这就对了
There you go!
我快吐了!
I'm gonna throw up!